{
    "question": "Do-mind- if-i- drink- you- coffe. the best arrangement is",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Do you mind if i drink coffee</p><p></p><p>maaf jika salah</p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "analyze-the-texts-below-to-answer-the-question-number-6-text-b-t-801",
            "question": "Analyze the texts below to answer the question number 6!    Text B\r\nText A\r\nI only slept for three hours last night At ten, we heard Last Saturday, my little sister, Dina, did something\r\na cry from Mrs. Wayan's home. She is our next-door funny. She got up very late, at six. She ran fast to the\r\nneighbour She's 70 years old and very weak. She lives bathroom. She thought she would be late to school\r\n. She\r\nalone We went there quickly, and we found her on the forgot it was Saturday. She took a very quick bath, got\r\nfloor\r\n. She just fell She could not move her hands and dressed, took her bag, and ran off to school. She did not\r\nher legs. At 10.30, my parents and I took Mrs. Wayan even have breakfast. After walking for five minutes, she\r\nto hospital. My father and I sat in the front seats. In the noticed that no other children were going to school\r\nback seats, my mum was holding Mrs. Wayan. In the Soon she realized it was Saturday! So, she walked back\r\nemergency room, a doctor examined her. Then, he said\r\nhome. We all laughed at her when she got home. She\r\nMrs. Wayan had to stay in the hospital. When she was also laughed at herself. Then she changed her clothes\r\nalready in the ward, we went home. It was 2 am. and went back to bed! My naughty sister!\r\n sebutkan kata benda dari dua teks tersebut. minimal 3\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>hands, bag, seats, clothes, legs</p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>smga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>bag,bed,dress</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "read-the-dialog-and-answer-the-questions-number-2-to-4-onci-do-y-402",
            "question": "Read the dialog and answer the questions number 2 to 4.    Onci\r\nDo you know where Clara is?\r\nDafa She is in our school library. She went there with Ms. Nina, our school librarian, a few\r\nminutes ago\r\nOnci\r\nDafa\r\nWhat does she do in the library?\r\nShe helps Ms. Nina and Mr. Eko to check and arrange the books. She usually also helps the\r\nlibrary visitors to find some books. She always is in the library on Monday and Wednesday.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Kak pertanyaannya mana? ga bisa jawab</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "danui-need-to-pee-where-is-the-ramathis-way-it-is-on-t-289",
            "question": "Danu:I need to pee. where is the......?    rama:this way, It is on the left side\r\nA. kitchen\r\nB. bedroom\r\nC. toilet\r\nD. garage\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Pee adalah pipis, maka kalau ingin pipis kita harus ke</p><p>C. Toilet</p><p></p><p>jadikan jawaban terbaik</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "edo-hello-im-in-airport-now-but-i-still-cant-find-your-311",
            "question": "Edo : Hello, I\u2019m in airport now. But I still can\u2019t find your sister. What does she look like? Dewi : She is tall. He has ... hair.\u00a0*    secepatnya yaaaaaa\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Brown/Black</p><p></p><p>Maaf kalau salah semoga menjadi jawaban terbaik ya :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "the-sentences-below-in-indirect-speechanisa-said-i-will-have-cal-341",
            "question": "The sentences below in indirect speech,anisa said i will have called my mother",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>anisa said that she will has called her mother</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "fill-i-the-blanks-with-the-form-of-positive-degree-964",
            "question": "Fill i the blanks with the form of positive degree",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>jawabannya adalah</p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p>gak tau</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "thankyou-momy-you-for-risking-your-life-your-useless-doughter-thi-535",
            "question": "Thankyou momy you for risking your life your useless doughter this love",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p> Terima kasih ibu, kau telah mempertaruhkan nyawamu demi cintamu yang tak berguna ini</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-tell-the-qualities-of-the-things-and-rooms-tha-t-you-have-in-y-352",
            "question": "1. Tell the qualities of the things and rooms tha\r\n\r\nt you have in your house !.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p> </p><p></p><p> </p><p>A </p><p>1.big</p><p></p><p>2.beutiful</p><p></p><p>3.room and they are awsome</p><p></p><p>4.small</p><p></p><p>5.nice</p><p></p><p>6.clean</p><p></p><p>7.clean and big</p><p></p><p>8.is green</p><p></p><p>B</p><p></p><p>1.big</p><p></p><p>2. my home</p><p></p><p>3.is white</p><p></p><p>4.big</p><p></p><p>5.clean</p><p></p><p>6.nice</p><p></p><p>7.nice and tidy</p><p></p><p>8.small and full of grass</p><p></p><p>9.big and nice</p><p></p><p>10.full of cars and motorcycles</p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p> </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Thing :</p><p>I have a laptop, you know what the use of a laptop is and its quality, while my bedroom is very beautiful and everything is neatly arranged</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "19-are-you-free-this-afternoon-what-does-the-underlined-mean-755",
            "question": "19. \"Are you free this afternoon?\"    What does the underlined mean?\r\nA. Have no body to do\r\nB. Have to do something\r\nc. have nothing to do\r\nD. Have lot things to do\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D. have lot things to do</p><p>semoga membantu </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "you-have-asking-your-family-member-about-their-habit-533",
            "question": "You have asking your family member about their habit\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>kamu telah menanyakan ke keluargamu tentang hobi mereka</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}